export default data = [
  {
      question: "You’ll need the store ______ to show proof of purchase if you want to return any items you bought.",
      options: ["credit","guide","license","receipt"],
      correct_option: "receipt"
  },
  {
      question: "Spending most of his childhood in Spain, John, a native speaker of English, is also ______ in Spanish.",
      options: ["promising","grateful","fluent","definite"],
      correct_option: "fluent"
  },
  {
      question: "The mirror slipped out of the little girl’s hand, and the broken pieces ______ all over the floor.",
      options: ["scattered","circulated","featured","released"],
      correct_option: "scattered"
  },
  {
      question: "No one knows how the fire broke out. The police have started an ______ into the cause of it.",
      options: ["appreciation","extension","operation","investigation"],
      correct_option: "investigation"
  },
  {
      question: "When there is a heavy rain, you have to drive very ______ so as to avoid traffic accidents.",
      options: ["cautiously","recklessly","smoothly","passively"],
      correct_option: "cautiously"
  },
  {
      question: "We decided to buy some ______ for our new apartment, including a refrigerator, a vacuum cleaner, and a dishwasher.",
      options: ["utensils","facilities","appliances","extensions"],
      correct_option: "appliances"
  },
  {
      question: "This math class is very ______; I have to spend at least two hours every day doing the assignments.",
      options: ["confidential","logical","demanding","resistant"],
      correct_option: "demanding"
  },
  {
      question: "One can generally judge the quality of eggs with the naked eye. ______, good eggs must be clean, free of cracks, and smooth-shelled.",
      options: ["Agriculturally","Externally","Influentially","Occasionally"],
      correct_option: "Externally"
  },
  {
      question: "The scientist ______ his speech to make it easier for children to understand the threat of global warming.",
      options: ["estimated","documented","abolished","modified"],
      correct_option: "modified"
  },
  {
      question: "The Internet has ______ newspapers as a medium of mass communication. It has become the main source for national and international news for people.",
      options: ["reformed","surpassed","promoted","convinced"],
      correct_option: "surpassed"
  },
]